[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "orange",
        "back": "апельсин",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "bed",
        "back": "кровать",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "table",
        "back": "стол",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "pen",
        "back": "ручка",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "white",
        "back": "белый",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "green",
        "back": "зеленый",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "blue",
        "back": "синий",
        "setName" : "English"
    },
{
    "id": 10,
    "front": "black",
    "back": "черный",
    "setName" : "English"
},
{
    "id": 11,
    "front": "pansil",
    "back": "карандаш",
    "setName" : "English"
},
{
    "id": 12,
    "front": "p",
    "back": "абцац",
    "setName" : "tags"
},
{
    "id": 13,
    "front": "a",
    "back": "ссылка",
    "setName" : "tags"
},
{
    "id": 14,
    "front": "img",
    "back": "картинка",
    "setName" : "tags"
},
{
    "id": 15,
    "front": "border",
    "back": "рамка",
    "setName" : "css"
},
{
    "id": 16,
    "front": "background",
    "back": "фон",
    "setName" : "css"
}
]
